<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fight for the Future</title>
    <description>Fight for the Future is dedicated to protecting and expanding the Internet&#39;s transformative power in our lives by creating civic campaigns that are engaging for millions of people.</description>
    <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.fightforthefuture.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Chelsea Manning Begins Hunger Strike to Protest Bullying by Prison and US Government</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Immediate Release&lt;/b&gt;: September 9, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact&lt;/b&gt;: Christina DiPasquale, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@balestramedia.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: Fight for the Future has launched a petition supporting Chelsea in her hunger strike. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://actionnetwork.org/petitions/stand-with-chelsea-manning-on-hunger-strike&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See the petition here. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, after years of requesting the care she needs for gender dysphoria, Chelsea Manning has released a statement about the start of her hunger strike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea is demanding written assurances from the Army she will receive all of the medically prescribed recommendations for her gender dysphoria and that the “high tech bullying” will stop. “High tech bullying,” is what Chelsea describes as “the constant, deliberate and overzealous administrative scrutiny by prison and military officials.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following her sentencing, Chelsea has respectfully requested that the US Government give her treatment for her gender dysphoria. Over a year later, Chelsea filed a lawsuit in September of 2014, where she sued the government to get a battery of treatments. As a result, she began hormone therapy in February of 2015.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;However, the military has been making her cut her hair to the male length and grooming standards. As part of her treatment, her doctors recommended that she follow the military prison&amp;rsquo;s female hair grooming standards. In September of 2015 she amended her lawsuit, asking that the government allow her to grow her hair. The government’s response in December 2015 was &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo; The case is still active before a DC District court judge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Statement from Chelsea Manning:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I need help. I am not getting any. I have asked for help time and time again for six years and through five separate confinement locations. My request has only been ignored, delayed, mocked, given trinkets and lip service by the prison, the military, and this administration.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I need help. I needed help earlier this year. I was driven to suicide by the lack of care for my gender dysphoria that I have been desperate for. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get any. I still haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten any.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I needed help. Yet, instead I am now being punished for surviving my attempt. When I was a child, my father would beat me repeatedly for simply not being masculine enough. I was told to stop crying—to &amp;quot;suck it up.&amp;rdquo; But, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop crying. The pain just got worse and worse. Until finally, I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t take the pain anymore.&amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I needed help, but no one came then. No one is coming now.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Today, I have decided that I am no longer going to be bullied by this prison—or by anyone within the U.S. government. I have asked for nothing but the dignity and respect—that I once actually believed would be provided for—afforded to any living human being.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I do not believe that this should be dependent on any arbitrary factors—whether you are cisgender or transgender; service member or civilian, citizen or non-citizen. In response to virtually every request, I have been granted limited, if any, dignity and respect—just more pain and anguish.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am no longer asking. Now, I am demanding. As of 12:01 am Central Daylight Time on September 9, 2016, and until I am given minimum standards of dignity, respect, and humanity, I shall—refuse to voluntarily cut or shorten my hair in any way; consume any food or drink voluntarily, except for water and currently prescribed medications; and comply with all rules, regulations, laws, and orders that are not related to the two things I have mentioned.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;This is a peaceful act. I intend to keep it as peaceful and non-violent, on my end, as possible. Any physical harm that should come to me at the hands of military or civilian staff will be unnecessary and vindictive. I will not physically resist or in any way harm another person. I have also submitted a &amp;quot;do not resuscitate&amp;rdquo; letter that is effective immediately. This shall include any attempts to forcibly cut or shorten my hair or to forcibly feed me by any medical or pseudo-medical means.&amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Until I am shown dignity and respect as a human again, I shall endure this pain before me. I am prepared for this mentally and emotionally. I expect that this ordeal will last for a long time. Quite possibly until my permanent incapacitation or death. I am ready for this.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I need help. Please, give me help.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 16:21:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-09-chelsea-manning-begins-hunger-strike-to-protest/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-09-chelsea-manning-begins-hunger-strike-to-protest/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NEW VIDEO: celebrities, comedians, musicians, speak out against Trans-Pacific Partnership on Rock Against the TPP tour</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2F9ugC4NG1Zoc&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9ugC4NG1Zoc?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: September 6, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organizers of the nationwide Rock Against the TPP celebrity concert tour––which seeks to harness the power of music and culture to sound the alarm about the anti-democratic Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement––have released a new video featuring footage from recent stops in Seattle and Portland where the tour drew large crowds, and performances and interviews with well known artists including hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt;, comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, Navajo punk band &lt;b&gt;Sihasin&lt;/b&gt;, and Danbert Nobacon of UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the new video here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/9ugC4NG1Zoc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/9ugC4NG1Zoc&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour kicked off in Denver in July and has stopped in San Diego, Seattle, and Portland. Upcoming stops include San Francisco this Friday at an event featuring revolutionary hip hop legends Dead Prez, followed by stops in Toronto, Boston, and Washington, DC. High profile participants in the tour have included Rage Against the Machine / Prophets of Rage guitarist Tom Morello, popular punk band Anti-Flag, golden globe nominated actress Evangeline Lilly, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Artists have a very special place because we have a platform we can voice the struggle. We can voice the people that dedicate their lives to the struggle. We can voice the people that’s on the front lines,” &lt;b&gt;says hip hop legend Talib Kweli during his performance.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As indigenous people, we’re kind of like the canaries in the coal mine. When there is environmental destruction, when there are corporations that are coming after our natural resources, as indigenous people we’re usually the ones on the front lines,” &lt;b&gt;Jeneda Benally of the Navajo punk band Sihasin explains in her interview. Her brother, Clayson Benally, added,&lt;/b&gt; “When you give corporations total authority and power to change laws, that’s going too far. When they first come to strip away our rights, who’s next?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The TPP is a corporate protection agreement that increases the rights of corporations and supersedes existing laws in nations that bind themselves to the contract,” &lt;b&gt;says Hawaiian slack-guitar legend Makana in the video,&lt;/b&gt; “it basically gives corporations a free pass to do whatever they want.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People are more willing to listen to a musician or a comedian or a poet because they appreciate other elements. They appreciate laughter, they appreciate the music, they appreciate how something is written,” &lt;b&gt;said comedian Hari Kondabolu,&lt;/b&gt; “So if you’re somebody who’s already on board, it’s inspiring, right? People say you’re preaching to the choir, but sometimes the choir needs that. And then for folks who aren’t in the movement, who don’t see a lot of this stuff, to be in that space and actually question themselves in a way that they’re not being yelled at is another way to get the message.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s basically just a money grab,&amp;rdquo; &lt;b&gt;said Danbert Nobacon of Chumbawamba, &lt;/b&gt;&amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s transferring wealth from the taxpayers to corporations who are not even in the same country.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP has little to do with trade, but instead grants multinational corporations extraordinary new powers to threaten jobs, the environment, affordable medicine, free speech, and food safety. The Rock Against the TPP tour brings together a broad coalition of supporters including digital rights groups, labor unions, environmental groups, and small businesses, and is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour is organized by digital rights group Fight for the Future and Firebrand Records, the social justice fueled record label from Tom Morello and Ryan Harvey. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 11:45:32 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-06-new-video-celebrities-comedians-musicians/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-09-06-new-video-celebrities-comedians-musicians/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” celebrity concert tour comes to San Francisco to protest Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release, August 29, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, (978) 852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Hip hop icons Dead Prez, actress Evangeline Lilly, punk legend Jello Biafra, Grammy winners La Santa Cecilia, and others to play free concert at Regency Ballroom on Friday, September 9th to protest anti-democratic TPP deal&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, CA––On Friday, September 9th, as part of the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour, prominent musicians will lead the charge in mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP), the unpopular and anti-democratic deal that has been a contentious issue in the 2016 election. The tour, which is the largest mobilization against the TPP in U.S. history, comes to Regency Ballroom from 6pm - 11pm for a FREE event featuring legendary hip hop duo &lt;b&gt;Dead Prez&lt;/b&gt;, actress Evangeline Lilly &lt;i&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt; punk icon Jello Biafra, Grammy winning latin-alternative band &lt;b&gt;La Santa Cecilia&lt;/b&gt;, riot-grrrl cellist Bonfire Madigan, and &lt;b&gt;Jeff Rosenstock&lt;/b&gt; of popular ska band Bomb the Music Industry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See more details and a full lineup here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/san-francisco-ca&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/san-francisco-ca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The concert will be followed by a teach-in on “How to Fight the TPP” on Saturday, Sep 10th from 1pm - 3pm at 1999 Bryant Street, hosted by experts from a wide range of organizations opposing the TPP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by digital rights group &lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt; in partnership with legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave) and riot-folk singer &lt;b&gt;Ryan Harvey&lt;/b&gt;’s record label Firebrand Records  previous stops on the tour have featured high-profile participants including &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt;, comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, legendary punk band Anti-Flag, Danbert Nobacon of the UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, Adult Swim comedian &lt;b&gt;Eric Andre&lt;/b&gt;, and ANTI records songwriter &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;. The roadshow has already drawn large crowds in Denver, San Diego, Seattle, and Portland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Trans-Pacific Partnership is not about ‘free trade,’ it’s about corruption,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future and lead organizer of the tour, &lt;/b&gt;“we’re harnessing the power of music and culture to sound the alarm about this corporate power grab and stop it in its tracks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TPP has little to do with trade, but instead grants multinational corporations extraordinary new powers to threaten jobs, the environment, affordable medicine, free speech, and food safety. The Rock Against the TPP tour brings together a broad coalition of supporters including digital rights groups, labor unions, environmental groups, and small businesses, and is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers. Organizers plan to announce additional dates to the tour soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional performers at the September 9th event include SF indie rock darlings Built for the Sea, Taina Asili, Ryan Harvey, Evan Greer, bell’s roar, and local hip hop emcee Raw-G.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.xkq7oohiw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE PHOTOS AND VIDEO AVAILABLE FOR USE BY PRESS HERE.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Interviews with Artists or Organizers, please contact Evan Greer at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or (978) 852-6457.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;# # #&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 09:34:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-30-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-30-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS: Rock Against the TPP Celebrity Concert Tour Draws Large Crowds in Seattle and Portland to Protest Trans-Pacific Partnership</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;607&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1081&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/669e83a68d95c6da5a94a906eb1d87a4/tumblr_inline_ocd3s1AtzY1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;607&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1081&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release, August 23, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Hari Kondabolu, member of Chumbawamba among participants, comedian Eric Andre makes surprise appearance&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the White House readies a final desperate push for the unpopular Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, large crowds turned out for &lt;b&gt;“Rock Against the TPP”&lt;/b&gt; events in Seattle and Portland over the weekend as part of a nationwide protest tour featuring high profile celebrities including actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt;, hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt;, comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu, &lt;/b&gt;and punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt;. TV’s Adult Swim comedian &lt;b&gt;Eric Andre&lt;/b&gt; made a surprise appearance at the Seattle event at Showbox SoDo, while the outdoor Portland event featured a street march with an inflatable TPP “death star.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS of the events available for use by press here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/WMeQZ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/WMeQZ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Short VIDEO clips are available at the bottom of this post, professional video coming soon.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both events also featured teach-ins hosted by Golden Globe nominated actress Evangeline Lilly (Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man), and a panel of local experts. The Northwest dates follow previous successful tour stops in Denver and San Diego.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, United Steelworkers. The Northwest events were organized with support from the Washington Fair Trade Coalition and Oregon Fair Trade Campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the large concert events and teach-ins, the tour has brought creative protests directly to lawmakers s by flying a 25 foot blimp over Congressional offices along the tour route. So far the blimp has been sited outside the offices of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-01-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rep Scott Peters’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; office in San Diego and&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-15-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25-foot/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rep Ami Bera’s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; office in Sacramento.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour stops next in San Francisco on September 9th at Regency Ballroom with an event featuring punk legend Jello Biafra (Dead Kennedys), Grammy winning latin alternative band La Santa Cecilia, and riot-grrrl cello legend Bonfire Madigan. Additional tour dates are to be announced. For more information see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;VIDEO CLIPS BELOW. Professional video coming soon. These clips are available for use by press. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crowd chanting “Hell No TPP” at Rock Against the TPP Seattle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FiupPQ6yv9qk&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iupPQ6yv9qk?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Downtown Boys at Rock Against the TPP Portland&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2F3Wq8v15dIiY&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3Wq8v15dIiY?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taina Asili at Rock Against the TPP in Seattle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2F2ZdP5L43Nh0&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2ZdP5L43Nh0?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crowd chanting at Rock Against the TPP Portland&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2Fn4Ws9PfpNg4&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/n4Ws9PfpNg4?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Navajo Nation band Sihasin performs an honor song for volunteers and artists:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FFgtw89AXnLc&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fgtw89AXnLc?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 08:33:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-23-photos-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity-concert/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-23-photos-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity-concert/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: Anti-TPP activists are flying a 25 foot blimp outside Representative Ami Bera’s Office protesting his support for unpopular Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/47aaa5a77e95978ae824bb466f99f1ee/tumblr_inline_obyl0kgyvE1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: August 15, 2016      &lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, press@fightforthefuture.org, 978-852-6457&lt;br/&gt;Contact on the ground: Tim Ellis, 773-458-0283&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bera faces backlash after recent comments in support of TPP. Activists fly blimp as part of awareness raising nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” tour featuring celebrities and musicians&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;SACRAMENTO, CA––8:00am PST: Activists involved with the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; celebrity concert tour are now taking their message directly to local lawmakers, flying a 25’ inflatable blimp outside Representative Ami Bera’s office at 8950 Cal Center Drive, Sacramento, CA, protesting the Congressman’s recent statements in support of the unpopular and anti-democratic Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See more PHOTOS and VIDEO of the blimp at the bottom of this post.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activists will remain outside the office with the blimp until 11:00am PST, ensuring that it’s visible to Congressional staff as they arrive for work this morning. They will be available for interviews about the action and the TPP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ami Bera turned his back on constituents when he voted to fast track the TPP.  We’re hoping a 25-foot blimp flying right outside his office makes it clear to him that supporting the TPP is betraying his constituents,&amp;rdquo; &lt;b&gt;said Robert Longer of CWA Local 9421.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In January, Rep. Bera failed to secure the endorsement of the local Democratic Party for his re-election to Congress, in large part due to continued constituent anger over his 2015 vote in favor of “fast track” legislation that will allow the TPP to circumvent ordinary congressional review, amendment and debate procedures.  He is among a small minority of congressional Democrats not publicly opposed to the TPP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The TPP is a back-room deal designed to rig the global economy even further in favor of corporate elites instead of working families,”&lt;b&gt; said Fabrizio Sasso, Executive Director of the Sacramento Central Labor Council.&lt;/b&gt; “Congress members who think they can side with Wall Street over their constituents on the TPP are going to be in for a rude awakening.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The airborne protest is part of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour, a nationwide series of large-scale concert, protest, and teach-in events featuring high profile musicians and celebrities like T&lt;b&gt;om Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Rage Against the Machine) Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt;, hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli,&lt;/b&gt; comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu,&lt;/b&gt; popular punk band Anti-Flag, Jello Biafra of the &lt;b&gt;Dead Kennedys&lt;/b&gt;, and Danbert Nobacon of &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;. The goal of the tour is to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, the unpopular and anti-democratic “trade deal” that has been a contentious issue in the Presidential election and at both of the recent political conventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello’s new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Private Internet Access, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and United Steelworkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See photos and video from the tour kick-off event &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;here.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour stopped in San Diego earlier this month, where activists &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-01-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25/&#39;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;flew the same blimp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; outside Rep Scott Peters’ office. The tour has upcoming stops in Seattle, Portland, and San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: press@fightforthefuture.org for more info.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3D0JdJS8LBkto%26feature%3Dyoutu.be&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0JdJS8LBkto?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/db7443bb5efd6479b1259f143cd96c92/tumblr_inline_obyl1nuxjo1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 12:14:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-15-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25-foot/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-15-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25-foot/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UPDATE: Celebrities Join Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” Concert Tour, Raise Awareness About Toxic Trade Deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Ftime_continue%3D1%26v%3DkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release, August 11, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, (978) 852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Actress Evangeline Lilly, guitarist Tom Morello, hip hop icon Talib Kweli, punk band Anti-Flag, Dead Kennedys singer Jello Biafra, comedian Hari Kondabolu, and Others Participate in Free Concert and Teach-in Series to Protest the Trans-Pacific Partnership&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next week, August 19th-20th, as part of the nationwide &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;tour, prominent musicians, actors, comedians and celebrities will lead the charge in mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP). The tour, which is the largest mobilization against the TPP in U.S. history, is comprised of a series of large-scale concerts, teach-ins, and protests, in an effort to educate the public about the unpopular “trade” deal that has been a hot topic in the presidential election. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lineups at each stop vary, with high-profile participants including Rage Against the Machine guitarist&lt;b&gt; Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt;, hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli,&lt;/b&gt; Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt;, Dead Kennedys founder &lt;b&gt;Jello Biafra,&lt;/b&gt; comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, legendary punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt;, Hawaiian guitar hero &lt;b&gt;Makana&lt;/b&gt;, Danbert Nobacon of the UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, Grammy winning Latin rock band &lt;b&gt;La Santa Cecilia&lt;/b&gt;, ANTI records songwriter &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;, and bilingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See details for upcoming events at the links below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 19, Seattle, WA&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/seattle-wa&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/seattle-wa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 20 Portland, OR:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/portland-or&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/portland-or&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;September 9, San Francisco, CA:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/san-francisco-ca&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/san-francisco-ca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organizers will be announcing additional dates soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America (CWA), CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, United Steelworkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.xkq7oohiw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE PHOTOS AND VIDEO HERE.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Interviews with Artists or Organizers, please contact Evan Greer at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or (978) 852-6457.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;# # #&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 17:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-11-update-celebrities-join-nationwide-rock-against/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-11-update-celebrities-join-nationwide-rock-against/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS: Chelsea Manning supporters deliver more than 100,000 petition signatures calling for no punishment following suicide attempt</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1280&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;958&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://65.media.tumblr.com/6ed6abba80f4ab413149a31a1d776550/tumblr_inline_obpflofuux1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1280&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;958&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE August 10, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact:&lt;br/&gt;Christina DiPasquale, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:christina@balestramedia.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;christina@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt;, 202-716-1953&lt;br/&gt;Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future, Demand Progress, RootsAction, Bill Of Rights Defense Committee, and Care2 delivered petitions to the Secretary of the Army Wednesday morning, Pentagon Papers whistleblower Daniel Ellsberg speaks out in support of Manning&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, DC––This morning Chelsea Manning supporters delivered more than 115,000 petition signatures to the Secretary of the Army Eric Fanning, calling for him to drop serious new charges faced by Ms. Manning as a direct result of her attempt to take her own life on July 5th. The petitions call for the military to provide Chelsea with adequate and humane treatment for both her gender dysphoria and her suicide attempt.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See more photos of the petition delivery below.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;On a press call following the delivery, Chelsea’s attorney at the ACLU, Chase Strangio, said:&lt;/b&gt; “Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s access to mental health care has been inconsistent. It is an ongoing concern of her attorneys and supporters that she is not getting adequate mental health care, particularly in light of the external forces that are destabilizing her mental health, like the service of these administrative charges against her and the ongoing investigation of those charges. It seems like the government is doing everything in their power to make her physical and mental condition worsen. Punishment for these charges could not only result in significant punishment, including indefinite solitary confinement, but also loss of access to the very things that connect Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s voice with the world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pentagon Papers whistleblower Daniel Ellsberg, said,&lt;/b&gt; “No harm has resulted from Chelsea Manning&amp;rsquo;s disclosures. Not giving her the proper medical treatment and then adding on these charges for her suicide attempt would seem designed to break her down as a human being. These charges appear to me to be sadistic and outrageous.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms. Manning attempted to take her own life in July after years of mistreatment in prison, and now the U.S. government is threatening to punish her further with serious &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;new charges&lt;/a&gt; directly related to her suicide attempt, which could lead to her being placed in indefinite solitary confinement, among other consequences. The 115,000 petition signatures came from petitions launched by grassroots activist groups supporting Chelsea: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freechelsea.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://act.demandprogress.org/sign/drop-the-admin-charges-against-chelsea-manning-now/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Demand Progress&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://act.rootsaction.org/p/dia/action3/common/public/?action_KEY=12415&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RootsAction&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://org.salsalabs.com/o/498/p/dia/action3/common/public/?action_KEY=20166&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bill of Rights Defense Committee&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thepetitionsite.com/766/997/768/tell-the-army-not-to-put-chelsea-manning-into-solitary-confinement-for-attempting-suicide/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Care2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, a similar petition effort helped &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/aug/18/chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-petition-drop-charges&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;draw attention&lt;/a&gt; to Chelsea’s situation when she faced solitary confinement for minor prison “infractions” including possession of an expired tube of toothpaste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The photos below are available for use by press, please credit: &amp;ldquo;Courtesy Demand Progress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;4000&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2992&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/d8d97829e6ed145e7f699ac8e380687f/tumblr_inline_obpflkuYBr1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4000&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2992&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;958&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1280&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/98cf85e3363491bee7cad05db84d0395/tumblr_inline_obpfjl8Wwa1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;958&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1280&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 14:18:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-10-photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-more/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-10-photos-chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-more/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PRESS CALL WEDNESDAY: Daniel Ellsberg Joins Chelsea Manning Attorney and Supporters to Call for No Punishment for Her Suicide Attempt</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Media Advisory For August 10, 2016&lt;b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact:&lt;br/&gt;Christina DiPasquale, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:christina@balestramedia.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;christina@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt;, 202-716-1953&lt;br/&gt;Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future, Demand Progress, RootsAction, and Care2 will deliver 100,000+ petition signatures to Secretary of the Army on Wednesday&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, DC––This Wednesday, August 10, Chelsea Manning supporters will host a press conference by phone at 12:00 noon EST on the charges faced by Chelsea Manning in connection to her suicide attempt and efforts being made by supporters demanding that Secretary of the Army Eric Fanning drop the charges against Ms. Manning, and provide her with adequate treatment for both her gender dysphoria and her suicide attempt.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The press call will follow the delivery of more than 115,000 petition signatures to the Secretary of the Army and will feature Chelsea’s attorney at the ACLU, &lt;b&gt;Chase Strangio&lt;/b&gt;, Pentagon Papers whistleblower &lt;b&gt;Daniel Ellsberg&lt;/b&gt;, Fight for the Future’s campaign director, &lt;b&gt;Evan Greer&lt;/b&gt;, who speaks to Chelsea on the phone regularly, and &lt;b&gt;David Segal&lt;/b&gt;, executive director of Demand Progress, who assisted with the physical delivery of the petitions to the Secretary of the Army.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;To receive call-in details, RSVP to: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:christina@balestramedia.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;christina@balestramedia.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms. Manning attempted to take her own life after years of mistreatment in prison, and now the U.S. government is threatening to punish her further with serious &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;new charges&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; directly related to her suicide attempt in July, which could lead to her being placed in indefinite solitary confinement, among other consequences. Signatures come from petitions launched by grassroots activist groups supporting Chelsea: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freechelsea.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://act.demandprogress.org/sign/drop-the-admin-charges-against-chelsea-manning-now/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Demand Progress&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://act.rootsaction.org/p/dia/action3/common/public/?action_KEY=12415&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RootsAction&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thepetitionsite.com/766/997/768/tell-the-army-not-to-put-chelsea-manning-into-solitary-confinement-for-attempting-suicide/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Care2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, a similar petition effort helped &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/aug/18/chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-petition-drop-charges&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;draw attention&lt;/a&gt; to Chelsea’s situation when she faced solitary confinement for minor prison “infractions” including possession of an expired tube of toothpaste. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chelsea Manning is a human being who deserves to be treated with basic dignity and respect,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“The U.S. government’s treatment of her will be remembered as one of the most shameful abuses of power in our nation’s history. Everyone who cares about human rights should be speaking out against this cruelty and injustice right now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Adding additional punishment on top of Chelsea Manning&amp;rsquo;s already unjust sentence, and threatening her with indefinite solitary confinement for attempting to take her own life, is an egregious miscarriage of justice,&amp;rdquo; &lt;b&gt;said Kate Kizer, campaigner at Demand Progress.&lt;/b&gt; &amp;ldquo;The government&amp;rsquo;s inhumane reaction to Ms. Manning&amp;rsquo;s attempted suicide is part of an ongoing pattern of mistreatment that appears to be an attempt to silence Chelsea’s important voice.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 09:07:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-09-press-call-wednesday-daniel-ellsberg-joins/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-09-press-call-wednesday-daniel-ellsberg-joins/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” Celebrity Concert Tour to Comes to Portland</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/08ff1a01296520d234704a1bc1143c77/tumblr_inline_obcj6jENrd1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: August 3, 2016      &lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:evangreer@gmail.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;evangreer@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Actress Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Hari Kondabolu, Makana, and more will lead free concert and teach-in to protest and raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership  &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portland, OR –Well known musicians, comedians, and celebrities will gather for a free concert event at Director Park on Saturday, August 20th from 5pm - 10pm. The lineup includes Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt;, comedian &lt;b&gt;Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, popular punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag,&lt;/b&gt; Hawaiian slack-key guitar legend &lt;b&gt;Makana&lt;/b&gt;, Danbert Nobacon of UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, and buzzworthy bilingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The free event is part of the nationwide &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;tour, a series of large-scale concerts, teach-ins, and protests mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, the unpopular, anti-democratic “trade” deal that has been a hot topic in the presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a full lineup and details for the Portland stop here: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/portland-or&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/portland-or&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS &amp;amp; VIDEO for use by press here:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and Oregon Fair Trade Campaign. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN: &lt;/b&gt;Saturday, August 20&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT:&lt;/b&gt; Free, festival-style concert featuring high profile performers and speakers from a wide range of organizations opposing the TPP. Food trucks. Beer garden. Kids games. 5:00pm - 10:00pm. Evangeline Lilly and TPP experts will host a free teach-in the following day, Sunday, August 21, at First Unitarian Church at 1:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO:&lt;/b&gt; Evangeline Lilly, Hari Kondabolu, Anti-Flag (acoustic), Makana, Downtown Boys, Danbert Nobacon of Chumbawamba, Son of Nun, Ryan Harvey, bell’s roar, Taina Asili, Naima Penniman of Climbing Poetree, Evan Greer, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE:&lt;/b&gt; Director Park, 815 SW Park Ave, Portland, OR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 14:30:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-03-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-03-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp-celebrity/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>August 19: Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” Celebrity Concert Tour to Comes to Seattle</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/08ff1a01296520d234704a1bc1143c77/tumblr_inline_obcjh8f8LU1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: August 3, 2016      &lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:evangreer@gmail.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;evangreer@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Hari Kondabolu, Makana, and more will lead free concert and teach-in to protest and raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership  &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seattle, WA – Internationally acclaimed hip-hop artist &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt; will perform with a full live band at a free concert at Showbox SoDo in Seattle on August 19th from 6pm - 11:30pm, as part of the nationwide &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour, a series of large-scale concerts, teach-ins, and protests mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, the unpopular, anti-democratic “trade” deal that has been a hot topic in the presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other high profile participants in the August 19th event include Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt;, comedian&lt;b&gt; Hari Kondabolu&lt;/b&gt;, popular punk band Anti-Flag, Hawaiian slack-key guitar legend &lt;b&gt;Makana&lt;/b&gt;, Danbert Nobacon of UK sensation &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;, Sierra Club executive director &lt;b&gt;Michael Brune&lt;/b&gt;, and buzzworthy bilingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a full lineup and details for the Seattle stop here: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/seattle-wa&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/seattle-wa&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;PHOTOS &amp;amp; VIDEO for use by press available &lt;/b&gt;here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.7qnmd3gmw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1#.7qnmd3gmw&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, the Teamsters, and Washington Fair Trade Campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN: &lt;/b&gt;Friday, August 19&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT:&lt;/b&gt; The day will kick off at 5pm with a teach-in and training hosted by Evangeline Lilly, followed by the Rock Against the TPP concert from 6pm to 11:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO:&lt;/b&gt; Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag (acoustic), Makana, Downtown Boys, Danbert Nobacon of Chumbawamba, Son of Nun, Ryan Harvey, bell’s roar, Taina Asili, Evan Greer, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE: &lt;/b&gt;Showbox SoDo, 1700 1st Ave S, Seattle, WA (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/The+Showbox/@47.6085655,-122.3415304,17z/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Map&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 14:22:18 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-03-august-19-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-03-august-19-nationwide-rock-against-the-tpp/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Government threatening to punish Chelsea Manning for suicide attempt generates widespread public outcry</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;572&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1251&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/b719f6104c8a92bda2de71f392862b94/tumblr_inline_obag1rwPST1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;572&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1251&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 2, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;More than 20,000 people have already signed a petition calling on the Secretary of the Army to drop new charges, provide Chelsea with adequate health care treatment. Celebrities including John Cusack, Pamela Anderson, Wil Wheaton, Margaret Cho, Sean Ono Lennon, weigh in&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In just a matter of days, tens of thousands of people have expressed their outrage through a petition at &lt;a href=&quot;http://freechelsea.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;FreeChelsea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; after it was reported that the U.S. Army is threatening imprisoned whistleblower Chelsea Manning with indefinite solitary confinement and serious &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;new charges&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; directly related to a July 5th attempt to take her own life, following years of mistreatment while incarcerated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 20,000 people have already added their names, with more signatures streaming in every hour. &lt;a href=&quot;http://freechelsea.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;The petition&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is addressed to the Secretary of the Army, Eric Fanning, and reads: “Punishing Chelsea Manning for attempting to take her own life after systemic mistreatment is inhumane. Drop these new charges, and immediately give Chelsea access to adequate health care.” The page has spread quickly on social media, with celebrities like&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/johncusack/status/759889431696384001&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;John Cusack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;,&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pamfoundation/status/759047276455161856&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pamela Anderson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;,&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/margaretcho/status/759243674387701760&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Margaret Cho&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;,&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/seanonolennon/status/759441650640748545&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Sean Ono Lennon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;,&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/wilw/status/759171617347874816&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, and Rage Against the Machine guitarist &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/tmorello/status/760175996041658368&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, expressing their support for Chelsea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort was launched by digital rights nonprofit Fight for the Future, who have supported well-known transparency advocate Manning in the past, including through a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/aug/18/chelsea-manning-supporters-deliver-petition-drop-charges&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;petition effort&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; last year that successfully &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/127036786593/breaking-chelsea-manning-found-guilty-punished&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;kept her out&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of solitary confinement when she was facing similarly outrageous charges for “infractions” that included possession of LGBTQ reading material and an expired tube of toothpaste. They also organized supporters &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/135448091208/whistleblower-chelsea-manning-to-receive-5000&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;to send &lt;/a&gt;her &lt;/b&gt;more than 5,000 birthday cards last year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our message could not be more simple: Chelsea Manning is a human being and deserves basic human dignity and fair treatment,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, who speaks to Chelsea on a regular basis,&lt;/b&gt; “threatening her with further abuse and punishment immediately following her attempt to take her own life is cruel and inhumane, and appears to be part of an ongoing attempt by the Army to silence Chelsea’s important voice as an advocate for transparency and government accountability.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signatures are still streaming in to the petition effort, which Fight for the Future plans to deliver to the Secretary of the Army in the coming days. For more information on Chelsea’s current situation, see the ACLU’s latest&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclu.org/news/chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite-solitary-confinement-related-suicide-attempt&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, and this article in &lt;a href=&quot;http://boingboing.net/2016/08/01/chelsea-manning-on-facing-lif.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;BoingBoing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which was co-authored by Cory Doctorow and members of the Chelsea Manning Support Network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future is a digital rights group best known for organizing the largest online protests in history against Internet censorship, for net neutrality, and against government surveillance. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FightForTheFuture.org&lt;/a&gt;. Learn more about the Chelsea Manning Support Network here: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chelseamanning.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.chelseamanning.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 09:46:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-02-government-threatening-to-punish-chelsea-manning/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-02-government-threatening-to-punish-chelsea-manning/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: Anti-TPP activists are flying a 25’ protest blimp outside Representative Scott Peters’ office calling for him to oppose unpopular Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;768&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/464dd403e9e53e82fa38eff5529359cf/tumblr_inline_ob979p4Uoj1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;768&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: August 1, 2016      &lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, press@fightforthefuture.org, 978-852-6457&lt;br/&gt;Contact on the ground: Lizzy Jean, 314-629-0188&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Following awareness-raising Rock Against the TPP concert featuring high profile musicians celebrities, activists bring message against toxic trade deal to local lawmaker&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN DIEGO, CA––7:30am PST: Activists involved with the nationwide Rock Against the TPP tour, which stopped in San Diego on Saturday, are now taking their message directly to local lawmakers, flying a 25’ inflatable protest blimp outside Representative Scott Peters’ office at 4350 Executive Drive, San Diego, CA, calling for him to oppose the unpopular, anti-democratic, Trans-Pacific Partnership deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activists will remain outside the office with the blimp until 11:00am PST, ensuring that it’s visible to Congressional staff as they arrive for work this morning. They will be available for interviews about the action and the TPP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FUAYPWhlTjqk&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UAYPWhlTjqk?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scroll to the bottom of this post for more photos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At this point it’s clear: people from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly oppose the TPP, and most members of Congress are recognizing that,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“We wanted to bring our message to Scott Peters in a way that he can’t ignore, so what better way than flying a 25 foot blimp outside his office?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/2bebbbb53f9168d359507dab98ab1631/tumblr_inline_ob8k8jqdFC1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The airborne protest follows the latest stop of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour, a nationwide series of large-scale concert, protest, and teach-in events featuring high profile musicians and celebrities like &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt; (Rage Against the Machine) Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly&lt;/b&gt; (Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man), hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli,&lt;/b&gt; popular punk band Anti-Flag, and Danbert Nobacon of &lt;b&gt;Chumbawamba&lt;/b&gt;. The goal of the tour is to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement, the unpopular and anti-democratic “trade deal” that has been a contentious issue in the Presidential election and at both of the recent political conventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organized by legendary guitarist Tom Morello’s new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Private Internet Access, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, and the Teamsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See a photos and video from the tour kick-off event &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@fightfortheftr/photos-video-massive-crowd-giant-blimp-protests-trans-pacific-partnership-at-rock-against-the-1733f9ed1fa1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;here.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour stopped at Spin Nightclub in San Diego over the weekend with a concert and teach-in hosted by Evangeline Lilly and featuring Jolie Holland, Emma’s Revolution, Bonfire Madigan, and others. Organizers have announced additional stops in Seattle and Portland later this summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; ###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: press@fightforthefuture.org for more info. Photos and video in this post are available for use by press, credit: “Courtesy: Fight for the Future.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;4056&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2433&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/88ca17dbc0a5eb5657c2d361b3d18a10/tumblr_inline_ob8lb8OZEn1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4056&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2433&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/9413913d29dfd56ac20dde444767096e/tumblr_inline_ob8kpuRF5s1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/1aec4711f6a3f808e27a8a78b55add89/tumblr_inline_ob8kamwMx61ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/832b0f2fa820d4091c5d8cbd75dc5e78/tumblr_inline_ob8lcyfhr01ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/8f5e3ed49e0fed345f8f61825d49e8e1/tumblr_inline_ob8k9ewZAI1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;5248&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2952&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 11:02:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-01-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-08-01-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chelsea Manning faces new charges, indefinite solitary confinement, related to suicide attempt</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 28, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Christina DiPasquale, christina@balestramedia.com, 202.716.1953&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;U.S government has systematically abused imprisoned whistleblower, continues to deny access to gender related health care&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;LEAVENWORTH, KS––Imprisoned whistleblower Chelsea Manning reported to attorneys and friends that she received a document from&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Army officials today informing her that she is being investigated for serious new charges related to her July 5th, 2016 attempt to take her own life. If convicted of these bizarre “administrative offenses,” she could be placed in indefinite solitary confinement for the remainder of her sentence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea has been systematically mistreated by the U.S. government since she was first taken into custody in 2010, including long stretches of solitary confinement (which the UN considers to be a form of torture), which she was subjected to for 9 months, even before she had ever been convicted, and continuing to deny her the medical treatment she needs for her gender dysphoria, which medical experts have clearly stated is the only course of treatment in which she would no longer be suicidal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this time, Chelsea is not receiving adequate psychological counseling, as her course of treatment is constantly irregular and therefore less effective. Having uncertainty, from day to day, regarding what medical treatment she is even going to receive is stressful in itself, and is certainly not what someone recovering from a suicide attempt should be subjected to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea is a trans woman being forced to serve out her sentence in an all male maximum security prison. Although Chelsea tries to stay focused on her writing and advocacy, being a woman in a all male prison is dehumanizing and exhausting emotionally. It is unnecessarily cruel to threaten her with punishment while in this very vulnerable state. We must pressure the Secretary of the Army to take a personal interest and dismiss these absurd charges against Chelsea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These new charges, which Army employees verbally informed Chelsea were related to the July 5th incident, include: 1) “resisting the force cell move team,” 2) “prohibited property,” and 3) “conduct which threatens.”Chelsea dictated the complete contents of the charge sheet to a supporter over the phone. It is transcribed here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is deeply troubling that Chelsea is now being subjected to an investigation and possible punishment for her attempt to take her life. The government has long been aware of Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s distress associated with the denial of medical care related to her gender transition and yet delayed and denied the treatment recognized as necessary,” &lt;b&gt;said ACLU Staff Attorney Chase Strangio.&lt;/b&gt; “Now, while Chelsea is suffering the darkest depression she has experienced since her arrest, the government is taking actions to punish her for that pain. It is unconscionable and we hope that the investigation is immediately ended and that she is given the health care that she needs to recover.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the ACLU explains in a&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclu.org/news/chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite-solitary-confinement-related-suicide-attempt&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press release:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; “These new charges, which Army employees verbally informed Chelsea were related to the July 5th incident, include, ‘resisting the force cell move team;’ ‘prohibited property;’ and ‘conduct which threatens.’ If convicted, Chelsea could face punishment including indefinite solitary confinement, reclassification into maximum security, and an additional nine years in medium custody. They may negate any chances of parole.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The U.S. government’s treatment of Chelsea is a travesty. Those in charge should know that the whole world is watching, and we won’t stand idly by while this administration continues to harass and abuse Chelsea Manning,” &lt;b&gt;said Fight for the Future campaign director Evan Greer.&lt;/b&gt; The group advocates for civil liberties and free speech and collected more than 100,000 signatures last year when the Army threatened Chelsea with solitary confinement for possession of LGBTQ reading material and an expired tube of toothpaste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These charges are egregious and should be dropped immediately. Chelsea needs to be given the proper counseling, be allowed to grow her hair, and have her gender dysphoria condition treated seriously by the prison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 17:08:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-chelsea-manning-faces-new-charges-indefinite/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VIDEO: Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag + other celebrities Rock Against the TPP</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FkA9nIeVvcMw&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kA9nIeVvcMw?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE: July 28, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;tel:978-852-6457&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;978-852-6457&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Organizers of nationwide tour opposing the Trans-Pacific Partnership release new video featuring performances and interviews with high-profile artists opposing unpopular “trade” deal&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the heels of the Republican and Democratic national conventions where the unpopular Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement was a hot and contentious issue, organizers of the nationwide &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; tour have released a video featuring footage from the roadshow’s kick-off event in Denver, with interviews from notable artists including legendary guitarist Tom Morello (Rage Against the Machine, Prophets of Rage, Audioslave), Golden Globe nominated actress Evangeline Lilly (Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man), and popular punk band Anti-Flag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the short, &lt;a&gt;3:30&lt;/a&gt; video here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/kA9nIeVvcMw&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/kA9nIeVvcMw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video also features high energy performances from the &lt;b&gt;Flobots, Downtown Boys, Taina Asili, Evan Greer, Lia Rose, Ryan Harvey,&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Son of Nun.&lt;/b&gt; Upcoming stops on the tour feature hip hop icon Talib Kweli, songwriter Jolie Holland, and Danbert Nobacon of Chumbawamba.The next stop is this Saturday, July 30th, in San Diego. &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/san-diego-ca&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Details here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;In the video Tom Morello says, &lt;/b&gt;“The small Illinois town that the Morellos hail from, Marseilles, Illinois, was horribly affected by previous trade agreements like NAFTA. It used to be a thriving Mayberry-like town with factories all around. Now all the factories are boarded up &amp;ndash; people have to choose between working at Wal-Mart or going into the army. Those jobs have all gone overseas where people now work in sweatshops at, you know, subhuman wages in environmental conditions that are awful, all because of these previous trade agreements. We’re using our guitars, our drums, our basses, our microphones our turntables, our voices, to help inform people about the TPP, so that they can stop it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly says,&lt;/b&gt; “It’s been &amp;hellip; proven with conservatives and liberals that once people know about the TPP, they don’t like it. Canada’s democracy has been crumbling because of trade deals like the TPP. I’m standing on the other side of this, warning Americans: be smarter. Please, please, be smarter than we were on the other side of the border.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Sane, frontman of Anti-Flag, says,&lt;/b&gt; “We are against the TPP. It was negotiated in secret by corporate lawyers and lobbyists, and to me that is the antithesis of democracy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future and lead organizer of the tour, said,&lt;/b&gt;“This entire effort would not have happened without the free and open Internet. That’s why Fight for the Future has been so involved in this effort, we’re trying to protect this powerful platform that allows us to bring people together.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rock Against the TPP tour features a series of large-scale concert, protest, and teach-in events designed to sound the alarm about the Trans-Pacific Partnership, which has little to do with trade but grants multinational corporations extraordinary new powers to circumvent democratic process and threaten good jobs, Internet freedom, food safety, the environment, access to medicine, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour is organized by Fight for the Future and Firebrand Records, with support from Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Private Internet Access, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, and the Teamsters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a full lineup and list of upcoming dates here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More dates to be announced soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 14:12:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-video-tom-morello-evangeline-lilly-anti-flag/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-28-video-tom-morello-evangeline-lilly-anti-flag/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PHOTOS &amp; VIDEO: Massive crowd at Rock Against the TPP kick-off event in Denver</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;A huge crowd of music fans and activists from across the political spectrum came together last night in Denver for the kick-of of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour to sound the alarm about the toxic Trans-Pacific Partnership deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check back here for more photos soon. These are available for use by press, credit “Courtesy: Fight for the Future.” See larger versions of these photos here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/gallery/t2DeH&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/gallery/t2DeH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/331f618065f8dcf0a363df57a806540f/tumblr_inline_oatrlmrNMb1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/08ff1a01296520d234704a1bc1143c77/tumblr_inline_oatt2nj0sU1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3Dh9g7tIjjTWc%26feature%3Dyoutu.be&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/h9g7tIjjTWc?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FVhNvtdQwjAk&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VhNvtdQwjAk?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FXcIGcsg29q0&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/XcIGcsg29q0?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/902258b5c091ca5739cf20e6ca7a477a/tumblr_inline_oatt2zMmcj1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://65.media.tumblr.com/e4eb70919d269ae05a34082134584ef3/tumblr_inline_oatt5b3MvY1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;We held a rally outside the venue on an awesome truck with a stage that the Teamsters provided.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/27906455d962a29159f95664ee4b8d74/tumblr_inline_oattb2skxC1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/27807dc86705968f95bbbc0495af4277/tumblr_inline_oatte10Rws1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/ee747044ca73b75336398ea900dc4a2d/tumblr_inline_oattejo30W1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FaIG-gC3Fj-o&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/aIG-gC3Fj-o?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FkkREpAAJY80&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kkREpAAJY80?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;We flew a 25 foot blimp over the venue ahead of the rally to make our message clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1086&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;724&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://67.media.tumblr.com/f40bc5aa1473739eb234cbdaf936e6cd/tumblr_inline_oatr6kDhpq1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1086&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;724&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://65.media.tumblr.com/df9b8deecbf09a9cfe9acd0130ff5467/tumblr_inline_oattqtlMTq1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://65.media.tumblr.com/c626f5d25ba09fe5e8c980d5a3ae1014/tumblr_inline_oattq5Dl9a1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/ed1bc5c9514612e890b08f0757659d1b/tumblr_inline_oattqfFFzL1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3264&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2448&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check back soon for more photos and video. These are available for use by press, credit “Courtesy: Fight for the Future.” Stay tuned for additional &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tour dates: July 30 in San Diego, August 19 in Seattle, and August 20 in Portland. More TBA.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 12:02:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-24-photos-video-massive-crowd-at-rock-against-the/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-24-photos-video-massive-crowd-at-rock-against-the/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: Anti-TPP Activists are flying a 25’ blimp above venue in Denver where Rock Against the TPP concert tour kicks off tonight</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1086&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;724&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://66.media.tumblr.com/f40bc5aa1473739eb234cbdaf936e6cd/tumblr_inline_oasa60tto91ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1086&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;724&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;July 23, 2016&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Huge inflatable protest “blimp” soars above Summit Music hall, where Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Flobots, and more will appear at a free concert launching multi-city roadshow to mobilize against dangerous Trans-Pacific Partnership deal&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;DENVER, CO––1:00pm MST: Activists are currently flying a massive 25’ inflatable “blimp” above Summit Music Hall, 1902 Blake St, in Denver, CO where a broad coalition of musicians, celebrities, and organizations opposing the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) are hosting the kick-off of the &lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/b&gt; tour tonight. The blimp, which can be seen from quite a distance, features a message about how the TPP is the antithesis of democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See photos of the blimp action here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/IKevg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/IKevg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a short video of activists launching the blimp here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/cbk-eI9Lokc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/cbk-eI9Lokc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The raising of the blimp comes just hours before legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello &lt;/b&gt;(Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), popular punk band Anti-Flag, Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly &lt;/b&gt;(&lt;i&gt;Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man)&lt;/i&gt;, Denver-based hip-hop outfit &lt;b&gt;Flobots&lt;/b&gt;, and buzzworthy bi-lingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys&lt;/b&gt; will appear at a free concert in Denver at Summit Music Hall to mobilize opposition to the TPP agreement. The event will kick off the Rock Against the TPP roadshow, a nationwide series of activism-fueled music events designed to raise awareness about the dangers of the toxic deal, which was negotiated in secret with hundreds of corporate advisors. Organized by Morello’s new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, other stops on the tour feature well-known performers like &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli &lt;/b&gt;and &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;. The TPP has little to do with trade, but would provide multinational corporations with new rights and powers that threaten good paying jobs, Internet freedom, the environment, access to medicine, and food safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The events in Denver begin at 5:00pm with a rally and press conference outside Summit Music Hall, MC’d by Jonny 5 &amp;amp; Brer Rabbit of the Flobots. Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, and organizers of the event  will provide statements to the press. The concert then begins at 6:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a full lineup and Rock Against the TPP tour dates here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RockAgainstTheTPP.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the performances, the Denver concert will feature speakers from a wide range of organizations opposing the TPP including Lori Wallach, Director of Public Citizen’s Global Trade Watch, as well as speakers from Food and Water Watch, Padres y Jovenes Unidos, the Sierra Club, the Association of Flight Attendants, Conservation Colorado, Rocky Mountain Farmers Union, Standing Up for Racial Justice, United Steelworkers, Denver-based technology startup SecureSet, Communications Workers of America, Student Labor Action Project, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the kick-off event in Denver this Saturday, the tour’s organizers have revealed three additional stops in San Diego, Seattle, and Portland, OR, with more dates to be announced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Working people everywhere have had enough,” &lt;b&gt;said Tom Morello,&lt;/b&gt; “The TPP is nothing short of a corporate takeover of our democracy. That’s why people are rising up to stop it. Corporate lobbyists want to sneak the TPP through Congress quietly; that means it’s time for us to get loud.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This fight against the TPP is not about right and left, it’s about right and wrong,” &lt;b&gt;said Evangeline Lilly,&lt;/b&gt; “Whatever you’re passionate about, whether it’s human rights, internet freedom, climate change, or food safety, the TPP is a bad deal for humanity, and a threat to the future of democracy. The more people learn about the TPP, the less they like it. It’s our responsibility to sound the alarm, before it’s too late.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Tour is being organized by&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; the viral Internet freedom group best known for organizing the largest online protests in history against online censorship and in favor of free speech and privacy. &lt;a href=&quot;http://firebrandrecords.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Firebrand Records&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the new social justice infused record label co-founded by Tom Morello and Ryan Harvey, is acting as the tour’s artistic partner. The roadshow is sponsored and co-organized by a diverse coalition of groups fighting against the corporate power grab that is the TPP, including Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Private Internet Access, Public Citizen, the Sierra Club, SumOfUs, and the Teamsters. More than 30 organizations have endorsed the effort, including the Electronic Frontier Foundation, National Nurses United, and the International Brotherhood of Carpenters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional performers for the Denver kick-off include Firebrand Records artists &lt;a href=&quot;http://ryanharveymusic.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ryan Harvey&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.liarose.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lia Rose&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://sonofnun.net/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Son of Nun&lt;/a&gt;, Puerto Rican vocalist &lt;a href=&quot;http://tainaasili.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Taina Asili&lt;/a&gt;, and riot-folk singer / Fight for the Future campaign director &lt;a href=&quot;http://evangreer.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Evan Greer&lt;/a&gt;, the tour’s lead organizer. Speakers from a broad coalition of local and national organizations opposing the TPP will address the crowd, explaining the many dangers posed by the agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The TPP is not a trade deal, it’s a corporate coup––an attack on the future of democracy and free speech,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, &lt;/b&gt;“people from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly oppose it, and we’re going to fight not only to stop the TPP, but to make sure that decisions that affect all of us are never made behind closed doors in the future.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP Tour dates&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;See full lineups at &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RockAgainstTheTPP.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;July 23: Denver, CO w/ Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Downtown Boys&lt;br/&gt;July 30: San Diego, CA w/ Jolie Holland, Evangeline Lilly, Emma’s Revolution, Bonfire Madigan&lt;br/&gt;August 19: Seattle, WA w/ Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Downtown Boys&lt;br/&gt;August 20: Portland, OR w/ Anti-Flag, Evangeline Lilly, Downtown Boys + more TBA&lt;br/&gt;Additional dates TBA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Tom Morello:&lt;/b&gt; Incendiary rock guitarist and acoustic troubadour Tom Morello, known for his innovative guitar solos and thunderous chords, is a groundbreaking artist whether in his solo career or as an original member of the rock bands Rage Against the Machine and Audioslave, two acts responsible for multiple Grammy Awards and a combined 30 million albums sold worldwide. He’s released four solo albums as The Nightwatchman and formed the band Street Sweeper Social Club with Boots Riley of The Coup in 2009. Morello has also been recognized by Rolling Stone magazine as one of the “100 Greatest Guitar Players of All-Time (#26).” Morello has produced or collaborated with artists of diverse genres including WuTang Clan, Johnny Cash, Tool, John Fogerty, Anti-Flag, Public Enemy, Joe Strummer, Crystal Method, Calle 13, Dave Mathews Band, Johnny Cash, Linkin Park, Travis Barker and Pete Seeger. In addition, he joined Bruce Springsteen and the E-Street Band for their 2014 world tour in support of Springsteen’s studio album High Hopes (Columbia Records) on which Morello is featured on eight tracks.  Most recently, Morello has joined forces with fellow Rage Against The Machine bandmates Tim Commerford and Brad Wilk, as well as Cypress Hill’s B-Real and Public Enemy’s Chuck D and DJ Lord to form the band Prophets of Rage. The group came together as a politically charged response to 2016’s tumultuous election year and after three sold-out club shows announced the launch of a 35-city trek across North America this summer.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Evangeline Lilly:&lt;/b&gt; Evangeline Lilly is an actress best known for her role as Kate Austen in LOST and films including The Hurt Locker, Real Steel, The Hobbit and Ant-Man. Evangeline is also a cross-genre writer, who writes for multiple demographics, and is a published author of her children&amp;rsquo;s book series, The Squickerwonkers. With a background in International Relations and Political Science, Evangeline has long held a passion for social justice and is a strong advocate for Fight for the Future - and for democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Anti-Flag &lt;/b&gt;(performing an acoustic set): After more than 20 years writing smash hits about smashing the state, ANTI-FLAG has cemented themselves as the premiere political punk band around with an unparalleled ability to write high-energy, riffy, fist-pumping, sing-along anthems that never lose sight of the band’s anti-war, anti-imperialism, pro human rights ethos.  Equal parts circle pit and picket line, their blistering and earnest live show brings a sense of community to the stage that unites people of all backgrounds and struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Flobots:&lt;/b&gt; Denver, Colorado’s revolutionary hip-hop act Flobots bring it on real with their signature anthems dedicated to creating a better world. Since forming in 2005, Flobots have released three full length albums, toured throughout the US and Europe, and appeared on late night programs including The Tonight Show and Late Night. Flobots are internationally known for their 2008 platinum single “Handlebars” and widely recognized for using their music as an inspiration for social change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Downtown Boys:&lt;/b&gt; Downtown Boys are a bilingual political sax punk party from Providence, Rhode Island in the northeast United States. Rolling Stone called them &amp;ldquo;America&amp;rsquo;s Most Exciting Punk Band&amp;rdquo; and NME has declared them a Band to Watch in 2016. They write songs about smashing the prison-industrial complex, racism, queerphobia, capitalism, fascism, boredom, and all things people tell us that try to close our minds, eyes, and hearts. The band is known for their live performances, which are equal parts punk show, political rally, and religious revival. Frontwoman Victoria Ruiz delivers moving speeches between songs, working the crowd into an angry but hopeful frenzy. The songs themselves are delivered with an earnestness, fun, and intensity that&amp;rsquo;s stunned audiences on their tours throughout North America. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Fight for the Future: &lt;/b&gt;Fight for the Future is a non-profit with more than 1 million members dedicated to defending and expanding the Internet’s transformative power for good. They’re best known for their vibrant, viral campaigns, and for organizing the largest online protests in history against SOPA, for net neutrality, and against mass surveillance. Last year, the group drove tens of thousands of phone calls and emails to Congress opposing the TPP through its &lt;a href=&quot;http://stopfasttrack.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;StopFastTrack.com&lt;/a&gt; coalition page. They also made headlines for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WDKzwB8GhN0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;flying a 30 foot blimp&lt;/a&gt; opposing the TPP over Senator Ron Wyden’s town hall meetings in Oregon. Fight for the Future conceived of the Rock Against the TPP effort, and are leading the organizing of the tour, with support from a wide range of public interest groups, labor unions, and grassroots volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Firebrand Records:&lt;/b&gt; Firebrand is a bold new project from Ryan Harvey (Riot-Folk) and Tom Morello (Rage Against The Machine, Audioslave, Prophets of Rage) dedicated to the global release and distribution of radical, socially conscious music. In recent years, people around the world have surprised each other with their courage, strength, and willingness to stand against injustice, militarism, and corruption. And where there has been protest, there has been music. Born from these times, Firebrand gives a platform for such voices. We know that music alone does not change the world, but we recognize that it is an integral part of the movements that do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 16:09:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-23-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-23-breaking-anti-tpp-activists-are-flying-a-25/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More than half a million people tell European regulator to protect net neutrality: joining academics, technology leaders, and Web inventor</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;July 21, 2016&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Contacts: Holmes Wilson &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hw@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;hw@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; +1-614-465-6371&lt;br/&gt;Tiffiniy Cheng &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:tyc@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;tyc@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, +1-413-367-6255&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Public consultation on open Internet rules for Europe ends with a bang: academics, investors, startups (including founders of Skype, Soundcloud, and Shapeways), web inventor Tim Berners-Lee and &lt;b&gt;510,370 members of the public&lt;/b&gt; demand strong net neutrality rules. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE INTERNET—The numbers are in: the European net neutrality movement is celebrating a huge milestone with the submission of &lt;a href=&quot;https://savetheinternet.eu/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;over 500,000 comments&lt;/a&gt; to EU regulators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In just six weeks, the public consultation organized by the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications (BEREC), provoked an unprecedented response from the EU public. In their previous consultations, BEREC never received more than 100 hundred responses. By the 18th of July the number of responses totaled 510,370—a historic feat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This massive surge of comments from the general public comes on the heels of similar demands from a broad coalition of &lt;a href=&quot;https://cyberlaw.stanford.edu/blog/2016/07/126-leading-academics-europe%E2%80%99s-telecom-regulators-protect-open-internet-europe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;academics&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savetheinternet.eu/en/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;public interest groups&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://webfoundation.org/2016/07/four-days-to-save-the-open-internet-in-europe-an-open-letter/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;web inventor Tim Berners-Lee, joined by Harvard’s Lawrence Lessig and Stanford’s Barbara van Schewick&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.factory.co/net-neutrality&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;135 startups and investors&lt;/a&gt;, including founders of the major European startups Skype and SoundCloud, and US companies like Medium, DuckDuckGo, and Cogent Communications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago, major European telecom companies &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theverge.com/2016/7/10/12139700/telecom-companies-5g-service-european-union-net-neutrality&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;threatened to delay investment&lt;/a&gt; in the next generation of 5G mobile network technology unless regulators weaken the current version of the draft guidelines. But in the face of such a broad coalition and overwhelming public support, Europe’s telecom companies—however powerful—appear increasingly isolated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The public has spoken. Now the question is, who will Europe’s regulators listen to?” &lt;b&gt;said Fight for the Future co-founder Tiffiniy Cheng&lt;/b&gt;, “Will they listen to the powerful telecom companies? Or will they listen to the historic coalition of academics, innovators, small companies, and over 500,000 people who are calling for real net neutrality rules with no loopholes?&amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Letting ISPs charge for special “fastlanes”—while putting every site that can’t pay in a slowlane—would destroy the economic and cultural miracle that is the open Internet,” &lt;b&gt;said Fight for the Future co-founder Holmes Wilson&lt;/b&gt;, “We won this debate in the US, but now Europe is facing its own critical test. Who will win? Startups and everyday Internet users? Or powerful telecom and cable companies? Now that it’s clear where the public stands, we hope regulators will side with the public, but it’s too soon to tell.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Background&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Startups, investors, and public interest groups are seeking three specific changes to draft BEREC guidelines, before BEREC finalizes guidelines on August 30th:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. To clearly ban on anti-competitive forms of “zero rating” (i.e. the practice of exempting select applications from users’ monthly data caps) in the guidelines;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. To prohibit telecom companies from using the law’s legitimate exception for specialized service to offer paid fast lanes to Internet applications, content, and services that could function on the regular Internet, which would circumvent the law’s ban on fast lanes on the Internet.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. To strengthen the “traffic management” provisions to ensure that telecom companies can only speed up or throttle entire types of application, such as games, or video chat if there is no other, less discriminatory way to solve the traffic management problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Fight for the Future:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt; is best known for its work building &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Battle for the Net&lt;/a&gt;, the net neutrality campaign hub that was central to the victory for net neutrality rules in the US, and organizing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/sept10th&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;, an online protest for net neutrality that drove 760,000 comments to the US Federal Communication Commission in one day. To support the movement for net neutrality in Europe, Fight for the Future launched the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.savenetneutrality.eu/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SaveNetNeutrality.eu&lt;/a&gt; campaign, which contributed 44,987 signatures to the effort, by offering widgets—featuring a countdown and a “slow loading” icon—that any website or blog could install to help gather comments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 13:49:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-21-more-than-half-a-million-people-tell-european/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-21-more-than-half-a-million-people-tell-european/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TODAY: Musicians and celebrities kick-off nationwide concert tour protesting anti-democratic Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FjKGRYypHogo&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jKGRYypHogo?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;July 23, 2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Flobots, and more to perform at free concert in Denver launching multi-city roadshow to mobilize against dangerous “trade” deal&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;DENVER, CO––Today, Saturday, July 23, legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello &lt;/b&gt;(Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), popular punk band Anti-Flag, Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly &lt;/b&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man), Denver-based hip-hop outfit &lt;b&gt;Flobots&lt;/b&gt;, and buzzworthy bi-lingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys&lt;/b&gt; will appear at a free concert in Denver at Summit Music Hall to mobilize opposition to the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement. The event will kick off the &lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP &lt;/b&gt;roadshow, a nationwide series of activism-fueled music events designed to raise awareness about the dangers of the toxic deal, which was negotiated in secret with hundreds of corporate advisors. Organized by Morello’s new label,&lt;b&gt; Firebrand Records&lt;/b&gt; and digital rights group &lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt;, other stops on the tour feature well-known performers like &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;. The TPP has little to do with trade, but would provide multinational corporations with new rights and powers that threaten good paying jobs, Internet freedom, the environment, access to medicine, and food safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The events in Denver begin at 5:00pm with a rally and press conference outside Summit Music Hall, MC’d by Jonny 5 &amp;amp; Brer Rabbit of the Flobots. Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, and organizers of the event  will provide statements to the press. The concert then begins at 6:00pm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a short video about the tour here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/jKGRYypHogo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/jKGRYypHogo&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a full lineup and Rock Against the TPP tour dates here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RockAgainstTheTPP.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the performances, the Denver concert will feature speakers from a wide range of organizations opposing the TPP including &lt;b&gt;Lori Wallach&lt;/b&gt;, Director of Public Citizen’s Global Trade Watch, as well as speakers from Food and Water Watch, Padres y Jovenes Unidos, the Sierra Club, the Association of Flight Attendants, Conservation Colorado, Rocky Mountain Farmers Union, Standing Up for Racial Justice, United Steelworkers, Denver-based technology startup SecureSet, Communications Workers of America, Student Labor Action Project, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the kick-off event in Denver this Saturday, the tour’s organizers have revealed three additional stops in San Diego, Seattle, and Portland, OR, with more dates to be announced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Working people everywhere have had enough,” &lt;b&gt;said Tom Morello, &lt;/b&gt;“The TPP is nothing short of a corporate takeover of our democracy. That’s why people are rising up to stop it. Corporate lobbyists want to sneak the TPP through Congress quietly; that means it’s time for us to get loud.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This fight against the TPP is not about right and left, it’s about right and wrong,” &lt;b&gt;said Evangeline Lilly,&lt;/b&gt; “Whatever you’re passionate about, whether it’s human rights, internet freedom, climate change, or food safety, the TPP is a bad deal for humanity, and a threat to the future of democracy. The more people learn about the TPP, the less they like it. It’s our responsibility to sound the alarm, before it’s too late.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Tour is being organized by &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;, the viral Internet freedom group best known for organizing the largest online protests in history against online censorship and in favor of free speech and privacy. &lt;a href=&quot;http://firebrandrecords.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Firebrand Records&lt;/a&gt;, the new social justice infused record label co-founded by Tom Morello and Ryan Harvey, is acting as the tour’s artistic partner. The roadshow is sponsored and co-organized by a diverse coalition of groups fighting against the corporate power grab that is the TPP, including Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Private Internet Access, Public Citizen, the Sierra Club, SumOfUs, and the Teamsters. More than 30 organizations have endorsed the effort, including the Electronic Frontier Foundation, National Nurses United, and the International Brotherhood of Carpenters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional performers for the Denver kick-off include Firebrand Records artists &lt;a href=&quot;http://ryanharveymusic.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ryan Harvey&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.liarose.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lia Rose&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://sonofnun.net/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Son of Nun&lt;/a&gt;, Puerto Rican vocalist &lt;a href=&quot;http://tainaasili.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Taina Asili&lt;/a&gt;, and riot-folk singer / Fight for the Future campaign director &lt;a href=&quot;http://evangreer.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Evan Greer&lt;/a&gt;, the tour’s lead organizer. Speakers from a broad coalition of local and national organizations opposing the TPP will address the crowd, explaining the many dangers posed by the agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The TPP is not a trade deal, it’s a corporate coup––an attack on the future of democracy and free speech,” said Evan Greer, “people from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly oppose it, and we’re going to fight not only to stop the TPP, but to make sure that decisions that affect all of us are never made behind closed doors in the future.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP Tour dates&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See full lineups at &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RockAgainstTheTPP.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 23: &lt;/b&gt;Denver, CO w/ Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Downtown Boys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 30:&lt;/b&gt; San Diego, CA w/ Jolie Holland, Evangeline Lilly, Emma’s Revolution, Bonfire Madigan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 19: &lt;/b&gt;Seattle, WA w/ Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Downtown Boys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 20:&lt;/b&gt; Portland, OR w/ Anti-Flag, Evangeline Lilly, Downtown Boys + more TBA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional dates TBA.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Tom Morello: &lt;/b&gt;Incendiary rock guitarist and acoustic troubadour Tom Morello, known for his innovative guitar solos and thunderous chords, is a groundbreaking artist whether in his solo career or as an original member of the rock bands Rage Against the Machine and Audioslave, two acts responsible for multiple Grammy Awards and a combined 30 million albums sold worldwide. He’s released four solo albums as The Nightwatchman and formed the band Street Sweeper Social Club with Boots Riley of The Coup in 2009. Morello has also been recognized by Rolling Stone magazine as one of the “100 Greatest Guitar Players of All-Time (#26).” Morello has produced or collaborated with artists of diverse genres including WuTang Clan, Johnny Cash, Tool, John Fogerty, Anti-Flag, Public Enemy, Joe Strummer, Crystal Method, Calle 13, Dave Mathews Band, Johnny Cash, Linkin Park, Travis Barker and Pete Seeger. In addition, he joined Bruce Springsteen and the E-Street Band for their 2014 world tour in support of Springsteen’s studio album High Hopes (Columbia Records) on which Morello is featured on eight tracks.  Most recently, Morello has joined forces with fellow Rage Against The Machine bandmates Tim Commerford and Brad Wilk, as well as Cypress Hill’s B-Real and Public Enemy’s Chuck D and DJ Lord to form the band Prophets of Rage. The group came together as a politically charged response to 2016’s tumultuous election year and after three sold-out club shows announced the launch of a 35-city trek across North America this summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Evangeline Lilly:&lt;/b&gt; Evangeline Lilly is an actress best known for her role as Kate Austen in LOST and films including The Hurt Locker, Real Steel, The Hobbit and Ant-Man. Evangeline is also a cross-genre writer, who writes for multiple demographics, and is a published author of her children&amp;rsquo;s book series, The Squickerwonkers. With a background in International Relations and Political Science, Evangeline has long held a passion for social justice and is a strong advocate for Fight for the Future - and for democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt; (performing an acoustic set): After more than 20 years writing smash hits about smashing the state, ANTI-FLAG has cemented themselves as the premiere political punk band around with an unparalleled ability to write high-energy, riffy, fist-pumping, sing-along anthems that never lose sight of the band’s anti-war, anti-imperialism, pro human rights ethos.  Equal parts circle pit and picket line, their blistering and earnest live show brings a sense of community to the stage that unites people of all backgrounds and struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Flobots:&lt;/b&gt; Denver, Colorado’s revolutionary hip-hop act Flobots bring it on real with their signature anthems dedicated to creating a better world. Since forming in 2005, Flobots have released three full length albums, toured throughout the US and Europe, and appeared on late night programs including The Tonight Show and Late Night. Flobots are internationally known for their 2008 platinum single “Handlebars” and widely recognized for using their music as an inspiration for social change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Downtown Boys: &lt;/b&gt;Downtown Boys are a bilingual political sax punk party from Providence, Rhode Island in the northeast United States. Rolling Stone called them &amp;ldquo;America&amp;rsquo;s Most Exciting Punk Band&amp;rdquo; and NME has declared them a Band to Watch in 2016. They write songs about smashing the prison-industrial complex, racism, queerphobia, capitalism, fascism, boredom, and all things people tell us that try to close our minds, eyes, and hearts. The band is known for their live performances, which are equal parts punk show, political rally, and religious revival. Frontwoman Victoria Ruiz delivers moving speeches between songs, working the crowd into an angry but hopeful frenzy. The songs themselves are delivered with an earnestness, fun, and intensity that&amp;rsquo;s stunned audiences on their tours throughout North America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Fight for the Future:&lt;/b&gt; Fight for the Future is a non-profit with more than 1 million members dedicated to defending and expanding the Internet’s transformative power for good. They’re best known for their vibrant, viral campaigns, and for organizing the largest online protests in history against SOPA, for net neutrality, and against mass surveillance. Last year, the group drove tens of thousands of phone calls and emails to Congress opposing the TPP through its &lt;a href=&quot;http://stopfasttrack.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;StopFastTrack.com&lt;/a&gt; coalition page. They also made headlines for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WDKzwB8GhN0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;flying a 30 foot blimp&lt;/a&gt; opposing the TPP over Senator Ron Wyden’s town hall meetings in Oregon. Fight for the Future conceived of the Rock Against the TPP effort, and are leading the organizing of the tour, with support from a wide range of public interest groups, labor unions, and grassroots volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Firebrand Records: &lt;/b&gt;Firebrand is a bold new project from Ryan Harvey (Riot-Folk) and Tom Morello (Rage Against The Machine, Audioslave, Prophets of Rage) dedicated to the global release and distribution of radical, socially conscious music. In recent years, people around the world have surprised each other with their courage, strength, and willingness to stand against injustice, militarism, and corruption. And where there has been protest, there has been music. Born from these times, Firebrand gives a platform for such voices. We know that music alone does not change the world, but we recognize that it is an integral part of the movements that do.&lt;b&gt;The events in Denver begin at 5:00pm with a rally and press conference outside Summit Music Hall, MC’d by Jonny 5 &amp;amp; Brer Rabbit of the Flobots. Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, and organizers of the event  will provide statements to the press. The concert then begins at 6:00pm.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 12:26:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-21-today-musicians-and-celebrities-kick-off/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-21-today-musicians-and-celebrities-kick-off/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SATURDAY: Musicians and celebrities kick-off nationwide concert tour protesting anti-democratic Trans-Pacific Partnership deal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;youtube&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fyoutu.be%2FjKGRYypHogo&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; id=&quot;youtube_iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jKGRYypHogo?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=https://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br/&gt;July 21, 2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Flobots, and more to perform at free concert in Denver launching multi-city roadshow to mobilize against dangerous “trade” deal&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;DENVER, CO––This Saturday, July 23, legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello &lt;/b&gt;(Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave), popular punk band Anti-Flag, Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly &lt;/b&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man), Denver-based hip-hop outfit &lt;b&gt;Flobots&lt;/b&gt;, and buzzworthy bi-lingual rockers &lt;b&gt;Downtown Boys&lt;/b&gt; will appear at a free concert in Denver at Summit Music Hall to mobilize opposition to the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement. The event will kick off the &lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP &lt;/b&gt;roadshow, a nationwide series of activism-fueled music events designed to raise awareness about the dangers of the toxic deal, which was negotiated in secret with hundreds of corporate advisors. Organized by Morello’s new label,&lt;b&gt; Firebrand Records&lt;/b&gt; and digital rights group &lt;b&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/b&gt;, other stops on the tour feature well-known performers like &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;. The TPP has little to do with trade, but would provide multinational corporations with new rights and powers that threaten good paying jobs, Internet freedom, the environment, access to medicine, and food safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a short video about the tour here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/jKGRYypHogo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/jKGRYypHogo&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See a full lineup and Rock Against the TPP tour dates here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RockAgainstTheTPP.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the kick-off event in Denver this Saturday, the tour’s organizers have revealed three additional stops in San Diego, Seattle, and Portland, OR, with more dates to be announced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Working people everywhere have had enough,” &lt;b&gt;said Tom Morello, &lt;/b&gt;“The TPP is nothing short of a corporate takeover of our democracy. That’s why people are rising up to stop it. Corporate lobbyists want to sneak the TPP through Congress quietly; that means it’s time for us to get loud.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This fight against the TPP is not about right and left, it’s about right and wrong,” &lt;b&gt;said Evangeline Lilly,&lt;/b&gt; “Whatever you’re passionate about, whether it’s human rights, internet freedom, climate change, or food safety, the TPP is a bad deal for humanity, and a threat to the future of democracy. The more people learn about the TPP, the less they like it. It’s our responsibility to sound the alarm, before it’s too late.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Tour is being organized by &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fight for the Future&lt;/a&gt;, the viral Internet freedom group best known for organizing the largest online protests in history against online censorship and in favor of free speech and privacy. &lt;a href=&quot;http://firebrandrecords.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Firebrand Records&lt;/a&gt;, the new social justice infused record label co-founded by Tom Morello and Ryan Harvey, is acting as the tour’s artistic partner. The roadshow is sponsored and co-organized by a diverse coalition of groups fighting against the corporate power grab that is the TPP, including Backbone Campaign, Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth, the International Labor Rights Forum, Private Internet Access, Public Citizen, the Sierra Club, SumOfUs, and the Teamsters. More than 30 organizations have endorsed the effort, including the Electronic Frontier Foundation, National Nurses United, and the International Brotherhood of Carpenters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional performers for the Denver kick-off include Firebrand Records artists &lt;a href=&quot;http://ryanharveymusic.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ryan Harvey&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.liarose.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lia Rose&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://sonofnun.net/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Son of Nun&lt;/a&gt;, Puerto Rican vocalist &lt;a href=&quot;http://tainaasili.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Taina Asili&lt;/a&gt;, and riot-folk singer / Fight for the Future campaign director &lt;a href=&quot;http://evangreer.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Evan Greer&lt;/a&gt;, the tour’s lead organizer. Speakers from a broad coalition of local and national organizations opposing the TPP will address the crowd, explaining the many dangers posed by the agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The TPP is not a trade deal, it’s a corporate coup––an attack on the future of democracy and free speech,” said Evan Greer, “people from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly oppose it, and we’re going to fight not only to stop the TPP, but to make sure that decisions that affect all of us are never made behind closed doors in the future.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rock Against the TPP Tour dates&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See full lineups at &lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;RockAgainstTheTPP.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 23: &lt;/b&gt;Denver, CO w/ Tom Morello, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Downtown Boys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 30:&lt;/b&gt; San Diego, CA w/ Jolie Holland, Evangeline Lilly, Emma’s Revolution, Bonfire Madigan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 19: &lt;/b&gt;Seattle, WA w/ Talib Kweli, Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag, Downtown Boys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 20:&lt;/b&gt; Portland, OR w/ Anti-Flag, Evangeline Lilly, Downtown Boys + more TBA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional dates TBA.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Tom Morello: &lt;/b&gt;Incendiary rock guitarist and acoustic troubadour Tom Morello, known for his innovative guitar solos and thunderous chords, is a groundbreaking artist whether in his solo career or as an original member of the rock bands Rage Against the Machine and Audioslave, two acts responsible for multiple Grammy Awards and a combined 30 million albums sold worldwide. He’s released four solo albums as The Nightwatchman and formed the band Street Sweeper Social Club with Boots Riley of The Coup in 2009. Morello has also been recognized by Rolling Stone magazine as one of the “100 Greatest Guitar Players of All-Time (#26).” Morello has produced or collaborated with artists of diverse genres including WuTang Clan, Johnny Cash, Tool, John Fogerty, Anti-Flag, Public Enemy, Joe Strummer, Crystal Method, Calle 13, Dave Mathews Band, Johnny Cash, Linkin Park, Travis Barker and Pete Seeger. In addition, he joined Bruce Springsteen and the E-Street Band for their 2014 world tour in support of Springsteen’s studio album High Hopes (Columbia Records) on which Morello is featured on eight tracks.  Most recently, Morello has joined forces with fellow Rage Against The Machine bandmates Tim Commerford and Brad Wilk, as well as Cypress Hill’s B-Real and Public Enemy’s Chuck D and DJ Lord to form the band Prophets of Rage. The group came together as a politically charged response to 2016’s tumultuous election year and after three sold-out club shows announced the launch of a 35-city trek across North America this summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Evangeline Lilly:&lt;/b&gt; Evangeline Lilly is an actress best known for her role as Kate Austen in LOST and films including The Hurt Locker, Real Steel, The Hobbit and Ant-Man. Evangeline is also a cross-genre writer, who writes for multiple demographics, and is a published author of her children&amp;rsquo;s book series, The Squickerwonkers. With a background in International Relations and Political Science, Evangeline has long held a passion for social justice and is a strong advocate for Fight for the Future - and for democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Anti-Flag&lt;/b&gt; (performing an acoustic set): After more than 20 years writing smash hits about smashing the state, ANTI-FLAG has cemented themselves as the premiere political punk band around with an unparalleled ability to write high-energy, riffy, fist-pumping, sing-along anthems that never lose sight of the band’s anti-war, anti-imperialism, pro human rights ethos.  Equal parts circle pit and picket line, their blistering and earnest live show brings a sense of community to the stage that unites people of all backgrounds and struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Flobots:&lt;/b&gt; Denver, Colorado’s revolutionary hip-hop act Flobots bring it on real with their signature anthems dedicated to creating a better world. Since forming in 2005, Flobots have released three full length albums, toured throughout the US and Europe, and appeared on late night programs including The Tonight Show and Late Night. Flobots are internationally known for their 2008 platinum single “Handlebars” and widely recognized for using their music as an inspiration for social change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Downtown Boys: &lt;/b&gt;Downtown Boys are a bilingual political sax punk party from Providence, Rhode Island in the northeast United States. Rolling Stone called them &amp;ldquo;America&amp;rsquo;s Most Exciting Punk Band&amp;rdquo; and NME has declared them a Band to Watch in 2016. They write songs about smashing the prison-industrial complex, racism, queerphobia, capitalism, fascism, boredom, and all things people tell us that try to close our minds, eyes, and hearts. The band is known for their live performances, which are equal parts punk show, political rally, and religious revival. Frontwoman Victoria Ruiz delivers moving speeches between songs, working the crowd into an angry but hopeful frenzy. The songs themselves are delivered with an earnestness, fun, and intensity that&amp;rsquo;s stunned audiences on their tours throughout North America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Fight for the Future:&lt;/b&gt; Fight for the Future is a non-profit with more than 1 million members dedicated to defending and expanding the Internet’s transformative power for good. They’re best known for their vibrant, viral campaigns, and for organizing the largest online protests in history against SOPA, for net neutrality, and against mass surveillance. Last year, the group drove tens of thousands of phone calls and emails to Congress opposing the TPP through its &lt;a href=&quot;http://stopfasttrack.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;StopFastTrack.com&lt;/a&gt; coalition page. They also made headlines for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WDKzwB8GhN0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;flying a 30 foot blimp&lt;/a&gt; opposing the TPP over Senator Ron Wyden’s town hall meetings in Oregon. Fight for the Future conceived of the Rock Against the TPP effort, and are leading the organizing of the tour, with support from a wide range of public interest groups, labor unions, and grassroots volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Firebrand Records: &lt;/b&gt;Firebrand is a bold new project from Ryan Harvey (Riot-Folk) and Tom Morello (Rage Against The Machine, Audioslave, Prophets of Rage) dedicated to the global release and distribution of radical, socially conscious music. In recent years, people around the world have surprised each other with their courage, strength, and willingness to stand against injustice, militarism, and corruption. And where there has been protest, there has been music. Born from these times, Firebrand gives a platform for such voices. We know that music alone does not change the world, but we recognize that it is an integral part of the movements that do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 12:26:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-21-saturday-musicians-and-celebrities-kick-off/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-21-saturday-musicians-and-celebrities-kick-off/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Press Call Wednesday: Kick-off for Nationwide “Rock Against the TPP” Concert Tour: Actress Evangeline Lilly, Anti-Flag Frontman Justin Sane, and Jonny 5 of Hip-hop Outfit Flobots Hold Press Call for Tour Kick-Off</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;For Immediate Release: July 18, 2016      &lt;br/&gt;Contact: Matthew Groch, (202) 454-5111, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:mgroch@publiccitzen.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;mgroch@citzen.or&lt;/a&gt;g&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tour Headliners and Organizers Join Famed Pollster, Dr. Stanley Greenberg, with New Polling Data Spotlighting the Anti-corporate Trade Sentiment Galvanizing the Electorate&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT: &lt;/b&gt;This Wednesday July 20th at 1pm EST Golden Globe nominated actress &lt;b&gt;Evangeline Lilly &lt;/b&gt;(Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man), popular punk band &lt;b&gt;Anti-Flag &lt;/b&gt;frontman &lt;b&gt;Justin Sane&lt;/b&gt;, Jonny 5 of the Denver-based hip-hop outfit &lt;b&gt;Flobots&lt;/b&gt;, and famed political pollster &lt;b&gt;Dr. Stanley Greenberg&lt;/b&gt;, will hold a press conference via phone for the kick-off of the nationwide &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rock Against the TPP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; tour, a series of large-scale concerts, teach-ins, and protests mobilizing to raise awareness about the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) agreement. Organized by legendary guitarist &lt;b&gt;Tom Morello&lt;/b&gt; (&lt;i&gt;Prophets of Rage, Rage Against the Machine, Audioslave)&lt;/i&gt;, his new label, Firebrand Records and digital rights group Fight for the Future, the tour is sponsored by Citizens Trade Campaign, Communications Workers of America, CREDO, Demand Progress, Friends of the Earth the International Labor Rights Forum, Public Citizen, Sierra Club, SumOfUs, and the Teamsters. This kick-off press call comes days before the first free concert in Denver at Summit Music Hall on Saturday, July 23rd. The tour’s organizers &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-04-talib-kweli-to-play-free-rock-against-the-tpp/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;recently announced&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;additional stops in San Diego, Seattle, and Portland, featuring high-profile performers like hip hop icon &lt;b&gt;Talib Kweli &lt;/b&gt;and ANTI-records songwriter &lt;b&gt;Jolie Holland&lt;/b&gt;. The TPP has little to do with trade but rather its core provisions would provide multinational corporations with new rights and powers that threaten good paying jobs, Internet freedom, the environment, access to medicine, and food safety. While the artists will discuss the nationwide concert tour, Dr. Greenberg will reveal new polling data explaining the trans-partisan anger at corporate trade deals and examining what drives voter anger about trade deals like the TPP.          &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN:&lt;/b&gt; 1 p.m. EST, Wednesday, July 20th&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Evangeline Lilly, Actress (Lost, The Hobbit, Ant-Man, Hurt Locker)&lt;br/&gt;Justin Sane, Guitarist/Vocals, Anti-Flag&lt;br/&gt;Jonny 5, Flobots&lt;br/&gt;Evan Greer, Campaign Director, Fight for the Future, lead tour organizer&lt;br/&gt;Dr. Stanley Greenberg, Chairman/CEO, Greenberg Quinlan Rosner Research&lt;br/&gt;Lori Wallach, Public Citizen’s Global Trade Watch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CALL-IN:&lt;/b&gt; Please RSVP for Call-in Information &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP: &lt;/b&gt;Please RSVP to mgroch@citizen.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Upcoming Rock Against the TPP Dates:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 23:&lt;/b&gt; Denver, CO w/ Tom Morello, Anti-Flag, Evangeline Lilly, Flobots + more&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 30:&lt;/b&gt; San Diego, CA w/ Jolie Holland, Evangeline Lilly, Bonfire Madigan + more&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 19:&lt;/b&gt; Seattle, WA w/ Talib Kweli, Anti-Flag, Evangeline Lilly + more&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 20:&lt;/b&gt; Portland, OR w/ Anti-Flag, Evangeline Lilly, Downtown Boys + more&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional Shows TBD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.rockagainstthetpp.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 19:08:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-18-press-call-wednesday-kick-off-for-nationwide/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2016-07-18-press-call-wednesday-kick-off-for-nationwide/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

